[
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『م ي ن ا ت و  』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميناتو"
  } ,
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『ا و ر ت ش ي م ا ر و 』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": "اورتشيمارو"
  },
{
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ل و ف ي  』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "لوفي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『م ا ي ك ي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "مايكي"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ر و ب ي ن』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "روبين"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ل ي ف ا ي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ليفاي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『م ي ك ا س ا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『غ و ج و س ا ت ا ر و 』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": "غوجو ساتارو"
    },
    {
      "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سوكونا 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سوكونا"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ب ي غ م ا م 』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "بيغمام"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ك ا ي د و 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كايدو"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ا س ت ا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "استا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ي ز ن』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايزن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『س ا ن ي م ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "سانيمي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ت و م ي و ك ا 』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " توميوكا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『م ي ت س و ر ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " ميتسوري"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『س ا ن ج ي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سانجي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ا و س و ب』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوسوب"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ش ا ن ك س』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "شانكس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『م ي ه و ك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميهوك"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『م و ز ا ن』~────❖ 〙",
"response": " موزان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ا ك ا ز ا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " اكازا"
  },
  {
   "question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ه ا ن ك و ك』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "هانكوك"
  },
  { 
    "question":"〘 ❖─── ~『س ا ك و ر ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ساكورا"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ش ا د و』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "شادو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ش ي ن و ب و』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " شينوبو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『د و م ا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " دوما"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ك ك ش ي ب و 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " ككشيبو"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ت ا ن ج ي ر و』~───❖ ",
 "response": "تانجيرو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ن ي ز و ك و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "نيزوكو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ر ي ن ج و ك و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " رينجوكو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ش ي س و ي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " شيسوي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『م ا د ا ر ا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " مادارا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『س ا س ك ي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " ساسكي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ي ت ا ت ش ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايتاتشي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا و ب ي ت و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " اوبيتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ب ا ن』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "بان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ج ي ر ا ي ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "جيرايا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ت س و ن ا د ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "تسونادي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『س ا ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ساي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ت و ب ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "توبي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ك ا ب و ت و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "كابوتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ل ر ي ك ا ج ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "الريكاجي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『ا ل ا ك ا ت س و ك ي』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": "الاكاتسوي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غ ي ت و』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " المزز"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『م ي غ و م ي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميغومي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ي و ج ي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوجي"
},
 {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ف ي ج ي ت ا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "فيجيتا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『د ا ن ز و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "دانزو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『ش ي ك ا م ا ر و』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "شيكامارو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ل ا ي ت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "لايت"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『إ ل』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "إل"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『إ ن』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "إن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『د ي ث ن و ت』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ديث نوت"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ك ي ل و ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "كيلوا"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『و ن ب ي س ع م ك』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "ون بيس عمك"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『د ي م و ن ا س ت ي ر』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "ديمون استير"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『د ر ا غ و ن ب و ل』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "دراغون بول"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ه ي ن ا ت ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "هيناتا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ي م ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايما"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『د ر ا ك ن』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "دراكن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『س و ن غ』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " سونغ"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『م م ل ك ه ن ي ف ر ل ا ن د』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": "مملكه نيفرلاند"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ك ا ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "اكاي"
  },
  {    
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『ا ل س ي د ل و ف ي』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "السيد لوفي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『ا و ت ش ي ه ا ل و ف ي』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها لوفي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوراهارا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ك و ر ا ب ي ك ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "كورابيكا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ه ي س و ك ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "هيسوكا"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖─── ~『إ ي ل و م ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "إيلومي"
  },
  {   
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『غ و ن ف ر ي ك س』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "غون فريكس"
},
{
  "question":"〘 ❖── ~『ج ي ن ف ر ي ك س』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "جين فريكس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『س ا ب و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "سابو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ي س』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ك ي ز ا ر و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " كيزارو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『 ا ك ا ي ن و』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": " اكاينو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『ف ي ج ي ت و ر ا』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": " فيجيتورا"
  },
  {  
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『ا ل ج ي ر و س ي』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "الجيروسي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ت ي ت ش』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " تيتش"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『ا ل ز ب ا ل ه غ و ك و』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "الزباله غوكو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ج و ه ا ن』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "جوهان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ب ي ر و س』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "بيروس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ز ي ن و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "زينو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『م ي ر ي و م』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميريوم"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『م ي ن ا ت و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميناتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『 ب ي ت و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "بيتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ب و ف』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "بوف"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ي و س ك ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوسكي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ا ي ن و س ك ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "اينوسكي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『م ي ت ش ي ك ا ت س و』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": " ميتشيكاتسو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『ل و ف ي س ي ن س ي』~─❖ 〙",
"response": "لوفي سينسي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『غ ي ن ي ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "غينيا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『ا ل ه ا ش ي ر ا ه ي م ي』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "الهاشيرا هيمي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ز ي ن ت س و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "زينتسو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ك ا ن ا و』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "كاناو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ي و ت ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوتا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ك ا ك ا ش ي』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "كاكاشي "
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ي و ه ا ن』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوهان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『س ا ي ت ا م ا』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": "سايتاما"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─ ~『ا ل ل ح ي ه ا ل ب ي ض ا ء』~─❖ 〙",
 "response": "اللحيه البيضاء"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖─── ~『ن ي و ج ت』~───❖ 〙",
 "response": " نيوجت"
  },
  {
  "question":"〘 ❖── ~『م ل ك ا ل ق ر ا ص ن ه』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "ملك القراصنه"
  },
  { 
"question":"〘 ❖── ~『غ و ل د ي ر و ج ر』~──❖ 〙",
 "response": "غول دي روجر"
  }  
]